neulion.com 2019-02-16

# NeuLion Privacy Policy - Powering the Next-Generation Video Experience | NeuLion

At NeuLion, we are committed to delivering live and on-demand sports and entertainment. We have created this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, disclose and safeguard personal data in connection with NeuLion products and services. Email us at  if you have questions about our Privacy Policy. [tell me more](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716819#policy)

**  
How We Collect Information**[tell me more](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716819#collect)

We collect information about you from a variety of sources, including:

  * directly from you
  * from our vendors and business partners
  * from our platform customers
  * from third-party sources
  * automatically, from devices that you use to connect to our website and apps

**Information We Collect**[tell me more](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716819#Type)

The information we collect through our services and sites may include:

  * contact information
  * demographic information
  * other details you choose to provide when using our services

**How We Use Information**[tell me more](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716819#Use)

**** We use the information we collect to:

  * provide services you may request
  * operate our business
  * analyze the use of and improve our products and services
  * comply with laws, rules and our policies

**How We Share Information**[tell me more](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716819#share)

We may share the information we collect:

  * within our enterprise
  * with our service providers and business partners
  * with our platform customers
  * with customers using our website and applications
  * at your request or with your consent
  * as required by laws, rules and our policies
  * in connection with a merger, acquisition or another corporate transaction

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of NeuLion, Inc. and its affiliates (“NeuLion,” “we,” “us” and/or “our”) in connection with our websites, web applications and mobile applications that we offer directly to individuals (collectively, the “Sites”). This Privacy Policy explains the types of personal data we collect, how we may use and share the data, and the privacy choices that you have with respect to our handling of personal data about you.

If your country of residence is a member of the European Union (“EU”), NeuLion, Inc. is the controller of your personal data for the purposes of EU data protection law.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the products and services we offer to business customers.

**Click on the links below to jump to the different sections of our Privacy Policy:**

**How We Collect Information**   
We may collect personal data from various sources, including:

  * Directly from you, at your direction or with your consent
  * From companies that use our products and services, including to host content
  * From our vendors and business partners
  * Automatically, from devices that you use to connect to our Sites

**Type of Information We Collect**   
The types of personal data we may collect include:

  * Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, and phone number
  * Demographic informati­on, such as date of birth, gender, and zip code
  * Information about employment applicants' work experience, education, salary, languages spoken, countries in which the applicant is authorized to work, and other information the applicant provide to us when applying for a job (including other self-identifying information, such as veteran and disability status, gender, and race/ethnicity, which we are required to request to comply with U.S. laws and regulations). Please note that the provision of self-identifying information is voluntary.

**How We Use Your Information**   
We may use the information we collect to:

  * Respond to requests, questions and comments and provide customer support
  * Tailor the content we display to Site users in our communications, and in connection with the use of our Sites
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business, our Sites, and other products and services we offer (including to develop new products and services)
  * Offer products and services that we believe may be of interest to customers
  * Offer and administer promotions, sweepstakes, or other contests
  * Conduct market research
  * Analyze and enhance our communications and strategies (including by identifying when emails have been received and read)
  * Generate anonymized data for further data analytics
  * Process employment applications, as further described in the “Employment Applications” section below
  * Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and manage risk exposure
  * Enforce our contractual rights
  * Comply with legal requirements applicable to information provided by NeuLion job applicants, such as work experience, education, salary, languages spoken, and other details an applicant may choose to provide to us when applying for a job under our policies

We may also aggregate any personal information that we collect in connection with our Sites, such that the information is no longer personally identifiable or attributable to you. We may use such aggregated information for our own legitimate business purposes without restriction.

**How We Share Your Information**   
We may share the information we collect with:

  * Business partners
  * Platform customers
  * Service providers that perform services on our behalf or partners with whom we may collaborate, including: 
    * Customer service and support providers
    * Partners with whom we jointly develop or offer products or services
    * Advertising partners
    * Survey and market research providers
    * Analytics organizations
    * Technology providers (including technology support, email and web hosting providers, email and text communications providers, and mobile app developers)

We may also disclose personal data to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation, protect and defend NeuLion's rights or property, protect the safety of our customers and Site users or the public, or to protect against legal liability.

Unless prohibited by applicable law, we reserve the right to transfer the information we maintain in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. If we engage in such a sale or transfer, we will – where required by applicable law – make reasonable efforts to direct the recipient to use your personal data in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. After such a sale or transfer, you may contact the recipient with any inquiries concerning the processing of your personal data

**Our Legitimate Interests**   
We process your information given our legitimate interests in providing and improving our products and services. In addition, we process your information in furtherance of our legitimate interest in protecting the NeuLion platform, to measure the performance of our services, and to keep our products and services safe and secure for our users and customers. We may also process your information given our legitimate interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you products or services that may be of interest.

**Employee Applications**   
If you apply for employment with NeuLion via our Sites or business partners, we will use the information you provide to process your application, to monitor recruitment statistics, and to comply with government reporting requirements. We retain de-identified statistical information about applicants to help inform our recruitment activities. NeuLion is headquartered in the United States and employee and recruitment data is held there and in other NeuLion locations worldwide. If an applicant becomes a NeuLion employee, NeuLion will maintain a record relating to that person's employment (including information collected via the employment application) and provide additional information about our data practices in connection with employee data to the extent required by law.

**Minors**   
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 16. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 16, we will delete that information.

**Your Rights And Choices**   
You have certain rights and choices regarding NeuLion's processing of your personal data. We reserve the right to verify your identity in connection with any requests regarding personal data to help ensure that we provide the information we maintain to the individuals to whom it pertains, and allow only those individuals or their authorized representatives to exercise rights with respect to that information.  
To the extent provided by applicable law, you may withdraw any consent previously provided to us, or object at any time on legitimate grounds, to the processing of your personal data. We will apply these preferences going forward. In some circumstances, withdrawing consent to our use or disclosure of your personal data will mean that NeuLion may no longer be able to provide you with services

**Access to Personal Data**   
You may access the data we maintain about you by submitting a request to [privacy@neulion.com](mailto:privacy@neulion.com). If we grant your request, we will provide you with a copy of the personal data we maintain about you in the ordinary course of business, in a commonly used format. You may request to correct any errors in your personal data. We may reject your request to access or correct personal data, as permitted by applicable law. If we reject your request, we will notify you of the reason(s) for the rejection.

In order to access your personal data, we will require you to provide proof of your identity. This information will only be used for that purpose.

**Portability of Personal Data**   
Under certain conditions, you may request that we transfer your personal data to another company in the format in which we maintain it in the ordinary course of business. We may reject your request, as permitted by applicable law. If we reject your request, we will notify you of the reason(s) for the rejection.

**Deletion of Personal Data**   
You may request that we delete your personal data. We may reject your request, as permitted by applicable law. For example, NeuLion may be required by legal, tax or other reasons to retain your personal information in its business records. If we reject your request, we will notify you of the reason(s) for the rejection.

**Marketing**   
You may unsubscribe from receiving marketing or other commercial emails from NeuLion by following the instructions included in the email. However, even if you opt out of receiving such communications, we retain the right to send you non-marketing communications (such as information about changes to our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use).

**Cookies and Advertising**   
We, our service providers, and our business partners may also collect certain information about the use of our Sites by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons and other technologies.

We and our service providers and business partners may collect information about Site users' online activities over time and across third-party websites. Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based do-not-track (“DNT”) mechanisms, we do not respond to web browser-based DNT signals at this time.

The information that may be collected by automated means includes:

  * URLs that refer users to our Sites
  * Search terms used to reach our Sites
  * Details about the devices that are used to access our Sites (such as IP address, browser type, and operating system information)
  * Details about users' interaction with our Sites (such as the date, time, frequency, and length of visits, and specific pages accessed during the visits) ****

Web browsers may offer users of our Sites the ability to disable receiving certain types of cookies; however, if cookies are disabled, some features or functionality of our Sites may not function correctly. To support and enhance the services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties to serve advertisements, through the services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these ad networks and other parties. Advertisements served through the services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category, which may be inferred from information you provide to us, based on your services usage patterns, or based on your activity on Third Party Services (as defined in this Privacy Policy). We do not provide personal data to any ad networks for use other than in connection with the services. To learn more about ad networks and to adjust your preferences, please click [**here**](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising?DB_OEM_ID=30000).

Some of our business partners that collect information about your activities on our Sites may be members of organizations or programs that provide you with choices regarding the use of your browsing behavior for purposes of targeted advertising. For example, you may opt out of receiving targeted advertising on websites through members of the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [**here** ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?DB_OEM_ID=30000&c=1#!/)or the Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking [**here**](http://optout.aboutads.info/?DB_OEM_ID=30000&c=2#!/). European users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising on websites through members of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking [**here**](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/?DB_OEM_ID=30000), selecting your country, and then clicking “Choices” (or similarly-titled link). Mobile app users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising in mobile apps through members of the Digital Advertising Alliance by installing the AppChoices mobile app, available [**here**](http://youradchoices.com/appchoices?DB_OEM_ID=30000), and selecting your choices. Please note that we may also work with companies that offer their own opt-out mechanisms and may not participate in the opt-out mechanisms that we linked above.

For more information on how NeuLion uses cookies, please click **_[here](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211716963)._**

**Links to Other Websites and Third Party Content**   
We may provide links to other websites, services, and applications that are not operated or controlled by NeuLion (the “Third Party Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the Third Party Services. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy practices of any Third Party Services before providing any information to or through them. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the Third Party Service that provides the feature.

**International Data Transfers**   
We may transfer your personal data to countries other than the country in which you initially provided the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you are located outside of the United States, we typically transfer your personal data to the United States, where NeuLion is headquartered. The countries to which we transfer personal information may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information.

We may transfer personal data from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to countries that the European Commission has deemed to adequately safeguard personal information, in which case no additional safeguards are required in order to transfer this information. If we transfer your personal data to other countries, we will either transfer it subject to the recipient's compliance with standard contractual clauses, EU-US Privacy Shield, or Binding Corporate Rules, or with your consent to the transfer, unless we are permitted by law to transfer personal data without such formalities. You may contact us for a copy of the specific safeguards applied to the export of your personal data.

**How We Protect Information**   
NeuLion maintains administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal data we maintain against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

Despite such efforts, however, please note that no company, including NeuLion, can fully eliminate risks or guarantee the security of personal information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of information about you at any time, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal information or other data arising in connection with theft of the information or other malicious actions.

**Data Retention**   
Our retention periods for personal data are based on business needs and legal requirements. We retain personal data for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which the data was collected, and any other permissible, related purpose. For example, we may retain certain assignment details and correspondence until the time limit for claims arising from the assignment has expired. When we no longer need the personal data we collect, we either anonymize the information (in which case, we may further retain and use the anonymized information) or securely destroy the information.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**   
We may at any time in our sole discretion revise or update this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes on this page and indicate at the top of this page the date this Privacy Policy was last revised. You may read a current, effective copy of this Privacy Policy at any time by visiting this page. We will also notify you of any material changes either through a pop-up notice, email or through other reasonable means.

**Contacting Us**   
If you have any questions, requests or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@neulion.com](mailto:privacy@neulion.com) or using the following information:

NeuLion, Inc.

Attn: Privacy Rights Administrator

1600 Old Country Road

Plainview, NY 11803
